[{"id": "1", "question": "\u65b0\u7684\u4e00\u5e74\u5373\u5c06\u6765\u4e34\uff0c\u4eba\u4eec\u90fd\u5f00\u59cb\u5bfb\u627e\u81ea\u5df1\u5fc3\u4eea\u7684\u65b0\u8863\uff0c\u5982\u679c\u662f\u4f60\uff0c\u4f60\u4f1a\u9009\u62e9\u4ec0\u4e48\u989c\u8272\u7684\u65b0\u8863\u670d\u5462", "answers": ["\u7ea2\u8272", "\u9ec4\u8272", "\u84dd\u8272", "\u9ed1\u8272"]}, {"id": "2", "question": "\u5982\u679c\u9009\u53d6\u4f60\u7684\u65b0\u5e74\u5e78\u8fd0\u5143\u7d20\u4f60\u4f1a\u9009\u62e9\u54ea\u4e00\u4e2a\u5462", "answers": ["\u706b", "\u6c34", "\u5ca9", "\u6728"]}, {"id": "3", "question": "\u4f60\u89c9\u5f97\u81ea\u5df1\u76842021\u5e74\u662f\u4ec0\u4e48\u6837\u7684\u5462", "answers": ["\u523a\u6fc0\u7684", "\u7cdf\u7cd5\u7684", "\u7a33\u5b9a\u7684", "\u6709\u6311\u6218\u6027\u7684"]}, {"id": "4", "question": "\u57282022\u5e74\u4f60\u5e0c\u671b\u81ea\u5df1\u505a\u4e00\u4e2a\u4ec0\u4e48\u6837\u7684\u4eba\u5462", "answers": ["\u601d\u8def\u6e05\u6670\u7684", "\u52c7\u4e8e\u5192\u9669\u7684", "\u4e3a\u4eba\u6e29\u548c\u7684", "\u5fc3\u601d\u7ec6\u817b\u7684"]}, {"id": "5", "question": "2022\u5e74\u4f60\u6700\u5e0c\u671b\u5f97\u5230\u4ed6\u4eba\u7684", "answers": ["\u8d5e\u7f8e\u548c\u6b22\u8fce", "\u7406\u89e3\u548c\u6b23\u8d4f", "\u5c0a\u91cd\u548c\u63a5\u7eb3", "\u611f\u6fc0\u548c\u5c0a\u656c"]}, {"id": "6", "question": "\u65b0\u5e74\u4f60\u7684\u7236\u6bcd\u9001\u4e86\u4f60\u4e00\u672c\u4e66\uff0c\u4f60\u89c9\u5f97\u4f1a\u662f\u4ec0\u4e48\u7c7b\u578b\u7684\u4e66\u5462", "answers": ["\u5c0f\u8bf4", "\u6563\u6587", "\u4f20\u8bb0", "\u8bba\u6587"]}, {"id": "7", "question": "\u65b0\u5e74\u5927\u626b\u9664\u770b\u5230\u5149\u79c3\u79c3\u7684\u9633\u53f0\u4f60\u60f3\u517b\u4e00\u79cd\u690d\u7269\u4f60\u4f1a\u9009", "answers": ["\u4ed9\u4eba\u638c", "\u73ab\u7470", "\u94f6\u674f", "\u5927\u8471"]}, {"id": "8", "question": "\u65b0\u5e74\u65b0\u76ee\u6807\uff0c\u4f60\u60f3\u5728\u4ec0\u4e48\u5730\u65b9\u5ea6\u8fc7\u4e0b\u4e00\u4e2a\u6625\u8282\u5462", "answers": ["\u6d77\u8fb9", "\u8349\u5730", "\u90fd\u5e02", "\u96ea\u539f"]}, {"id": "9", "question": "\u4f60\u66f4\u559c\u6b22\u4ec0\u4e48\u53e3\u5473\u7684\u5143\u5bb5\u5462", "answers": ["\u7ea2\u8c46\u7684", "\u9ed1\u829d\u9ebb\u7684", "\u6842\u82b1\u7684", "\u65e0\u9985\u7684"]}, {"id": "10", "question": "\u65b0\u7684\u4e00\u5e74\u4f60\u6700\u5e0c\u671b\u81ea\u5df1\u54ea\u4e9b\u65b9\u9762\u6709\u8f83\u5927\u8fdb\u6b65", "answers": ["\u5b66\u4e1a", "\u4eba\u9645\u5173\u7cfb", "\u72ec\u7acb\u601d\u8003", "\u751f\u6d3b\u6280\u5de7"]}, {"id": "11", "question": "\u65b0\u5e74\u5168\u5bb6\u56e2\u5706\u5927\u5408\u5f71\u4f60\u4f1a\u9009\u62e9\u4ec0\u4e48\u6ee4\u955c\u5462", "answers": ["\u6668\u5149", "\u6000\u65e7", "\u6e05\u65b0", "\u4e0d\u7528\u6ee4\u955c"]}, {"id": "12", "question": "\u4f60\u6700\u559c\u6b22\u7684\u65b0\u5e74\u4e60\u4fd7\u662f\u4ec0\u4e48", "answers": ["\u5927\u626b\u9664", "\u56e2\u5e74\u996d", "\u653e\u7206\u7af9", "\u5b88\u5c81"]}, {"id": "13", "question": "\u4f60\u6700\u5e0c\u671b\u81ea\u5df1\u76842022", "answers": ["\u987a\u5229", "\u6539\u53d8", "\u5145\u5b9e", "\u597d\u8fd0"]}, {"id": "14", "question": "\u4f60\u89c9\u5f97\u4ec0\u4e48\u4e1c\u897f\u6700\u6709\u5e74\u5473\u5462", "answers": ["\u6625\u8054", "\u7a97\u82b1", "\u7ea2\u706f\u7b3c", "\u7ea2\u5305"]}, {"id": "15", "question": "\u8fc7\u5e74\u65f6\u4eb2\u621a\u6446\u51fa\u7684\u6c34\u679c\u4f60\u6700\u559c\u6b22\u4ec0\u4e48\u5462", "answers": ["\u82f9\u679c", "\u6a58\u5b50", "\u68a8", "\u6a59\u5b50"]}]